const essentialsChapter7QuizData = [
  {
    id: "7_1",
    question: "The venting system does what with flue gases? (Page 89)",
    options: ["Exhaust the flue gases and convey them outside", "Filters the gases", "Takes the flue gases and blows them into the home", "Takes fresh air into the home"],
    answer: "Exhaust the flue gases and convey them outside"
  },
  {
    id: "7_2",
    question: "The venting system protects the home from _________. (Page 89)",
    options: ["Hot and Corrosive flue gases", "Weather", "Animals", "Criminals"],
    answer: "Hot and Corrosive flue gases"
  },
  {
    id: "7_3",
    question: "As hot flue gases travel up the venting system and out of the home, there is an area of _________ pressure created inside the combustion chamber. (Page 89)",
    options: ["Negative", "Positive", "Neutral", "Hydraulic"],
    answer: "Negative"
  },
  {
    id: "7_4",
    question: "Negative pressure in the combustion chamber due to hot flue gases venting PULLS air into the appliance or fireplace. (Page 89)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "7_5",
    question: "_________ chimneys are often site-built and may be constructed of brick, concrete, blocks, stone, pre-cast material, or a combination of these materials. (Page 89)",
    options: ["Masonry", "Factory Built", "Homemade", "Non-Compliant"],
    answer: "Masonry",
  },
  {
    id: "7_6",
    question: "What is the max number of Hearth Appliances a flue should have? (Page 89)",
    options: ["1", "2", "3", "Unlimited"],
    answer: "1",
  },
  {
    id: "7_7",
    question: "A chimney can have multiple flues. (Page 89)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_8",
    question: "If a chimney has multiple flues, they should be separated by a masonry divider called a _________. (Page 89)",
    options: ["Wythe", "Separator", "Barrier", "Strife"],
    answer: "Wythe",
  },
  {
    id: "7_9",
    question: "Where can you find the current specifications for masonry chimneys including information on general requirements, specific construction details, termination (height) requirements, and clearance from combustibles. (Page 90)",
    options: ["NFPA 211 Only", "IRC Only", "NFPA 211 and IRC", "NFPA 211 and NFPA 54"],
    answer: "NFPA 211 and IRC",
  },
  {
    id: "7_10",
    question: "These are made from an extruded clay product and baked for strength and durability. (Page 90)",
    options: ["Terra Cotta Flue Tiles", "Chimney Crown", "Parging", "Hearth"],
    answer: "Terra Cotta Flue Tiles",
  },
  {
    id: "7_11",
    question: "Refractory cement is designed to hold its strength at temperatures of _________°F or higher. (Page 90)",
    options: ["2000", "1000", "500", "1500"],
    answer: "1000",
  },
  {
    id: "7_12",
    question: "NFPA 211 specifies _________ be used between tiles. (Page 90)",
    options: ["Concrete", "Non-Water-Soluble Refractory Cement", "Grout", "Nothing"],
    answer: "Non-Water-Soluble Refractory Cement",
  },
  {
    id: "7_13",
    question: "Terra Cotta Flue Tiles are usually _________ inch thick or thicker. (Page 90)",
    options: ["5/8", "1/2", "3/4", "1"],
    answer: "5/8",
  },
  {
    id: "7_14",
    question: "Terra Cotta Flue Tiles are usually _________ feet long. (Page 90)",
    options: ["2", "3", "2.5", "5"],
    answer: "2",
  },
  {
    id: "7_15",
    question: "_________ are composed of factory-made, field-assembled components of pre-cast masonry materials. (Page 90)",
    options: ["Modular Chimneys", "Stainless Steel Liners", "Chimney Chase", "Connector Pipe"],
    answer: "Modular Chimneys",
  },
  {
    id: "7_16",
    question: "Most factory-built fireplaces are tested to _________. (Page 90)",
    options: ["UL 127", "UL 103", "UL 1777", " UL 103-HT"],
    answer: "UL 127",
  },
  {
    id: "7_17",
    question: "When it comes to Factory-Built Chimneys, _________ is responsible to specify the minimum and maximum heights, the number of elbow or offsets that may be used, and the acceptable venting configurations. (Page 90)",
    options: ["The appliance manufacturer", "NFPA 211", "IRC", "Installer"],
    answer: "The appliance manufacturer",
  },
  {
    id: "7_18",
    question: "Some factory-built chimneys are double-wall pipe while others are triple-wall chimney pipe. (Page 90)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_19",
    question: "Most factory-built chimneys used for UL 127 fireplaces are tested to _________°F. (Page 91)",
    options: ["1700", "2100", "2000", "1500"],
    answer: "1700",
  },
  {
    id: "7_20",
    question: "Most factory-built chimneys used for UL 127 fireplaces are HT listed. (Page 91)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_21",
    question: "The UL 1482, Standard for Solid-Fuel Type Room Heaters, requires that the venting system be tested to _________. (Page 91)",
    options: ["UL 103", "UL 103-HT", "NFPA 54", "NFPA 211"],
    answer: "UL 103-HT",
  },
  {
    id: "7_22",
    question: "Freestanding wood burning stoves often use a _________ that goes from the flue collar on the stove to the ceiling, wall or fireplace where the conversion to the chimney takes place. (Page 91)",
    options: ["Draft Hood", "Baffle", "Connector Pipe", "Damper"],
    answer: "Connector Pipe",
  },
  {
    id: "7_23",
    question: "_________ is the most common type of connector pipe. (Page 91)",
    options: ["Single Wall Stovepipe", "Double-Wall Insulated Pipe", "Triple-Wall Chimney Pipe", "Terra Cotta Tile"],
    answer: "Single Wall Stovepipe",
  },
  {
    id: "7_24",
    question: "Today, single-wall pipe should be at least _________ gauge. (Page 91)",
    options: ["16", "24", "26", "22"],
    answer: "24",
  },
  {
    id: "7_25",
    question: "Stove pipe that requires the installer to assemble the pipe itself has something called a _________. (Page 92)",
    options: ["Snap Lock", "Seam Joiner", "Joint Connection", "Slip Seam"],
    answer: "Snap Lock",
  },
  {
    id: "7_26",
    question: "Single wall stovepipe requires _________ inches of clearance to combustibles. (Page 92)",
    options: ["18", "36", "12", "9"],
    answer: "18",
  },
  {
    id: "7_27",
    question: "Double wall connector pipe can be cut to size. (Page 92)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_28",
    question: "What kind of connector pipe can go through walls, ceilings, or any combustible material? (Page 92)",
    options: ["No connector pipe can do this", "6 inch and under", "Double Wall", "Triple Wall"],
    answer: "No connector pipe can do this",
  },
  {
    id: "7_29",
    question: "What happens to Terra Cotta Flue Tiles if subjected to rapid change in temperature (Thermal Shock), often associated with a chimney fire. (Page 92)",
    options: ["They can fracture or crack", "They melt", "The refractory cement in between the tiles melts", "Nothing, they are built with this in mind"],
    answer: "They can fracture or crack",
  },
  {
    id: "7_30",
    question: "According to NFPA 211, if the flue lining is damaged, repair or replacement isn't necessary. (Page 92)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_31",
    question: "Coating and repair systems repair joints in tile liners and resurface defecting flue tiles with refractory materials. (Page 93)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_32",
    question: "Double wall connector pipe can be cut to size. (Page 92)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_33",
    question: "Stainless steel lining systems come in 2 major categories; _________. (Page 94)",
    options: ["Rigid and Flexible", "Long and Short", "Sharp and Smooth", "Refractory and General"],
    answer: "Rigid and Flexible",
  },
  {
    id: "7_34",
    question: "_________ is defined as a mix of different metals or a mix of an element and a metal. (Page 94)",
    options: ["Alloy", "Catalyst", "Steel", "Refractory"],
    answer: "Alloy",
  },
  {
    id: "7_35",
    question: "_________ These alloys are best suited for wood and pellet burning applications and still being used. They are not recommended in gas, coal or oil burning situations. (Page 94)",
    options: ["304 and 304L", "AL29-4C", "316, 316L and 316TI", "321"],
    answer: "304 and 304L",
  },
  {
    id: "7_36",
    question: "_________ These alloys are often termed all fuel alloys (wood, pellet, coal, oil and gas). When it comes to gas, they are only suitable for Category 1. (Page 94)",
    options: ["304 and 304L", "AL29-4C", "316, 316L and 316TI", "321"],
    answer: "316, 316L and 316TI",
  },
  {
    id: "7_37",
    question: "_________ These alloys are suitable for wood and pellet burning applications. However, it is no longer being used. (Page 94)",
    options: ["304 and 304L", "AL29-4C", "316, 316L and 316TI", "321"],
    answer: "321",
  },
  {
    id: "7_38",
    question: "_________ These alloys are solely used for venting gas appliances and , in some cases, bio fuel appliances. (Page 94)",
    options: ["304 and 304L", "AL29-4C", "316, 316L and 316TI", "321"],
    answer: "AL29-4C",
  },
  {
    id: "7_39",
    question: "304 alloys are recommended for venting Gas appliances. (Page 94)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_40",
    question: "Most rigid liner sections are made of series 321 stainless steel. (Page 94)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_41",
    question: "Most rigid liner sections are typically 1-4 feet long. (Page 94)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_42",
    question: "What typically secures the joints on a rigid liner? (Page 94)",
    options: ["Stainless steel pop rivets", "Stainless steel screws", "Twist-lock fittings", "Any of these"],
    answer: "Any of these",
  },
  {
    id: "7_43",
    question: "Rigid liners are supported at the top of the chimney or the thimble area. (Page 94)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_44",
    question: "Rigid stainless-steel liners cannot expand vertically during the heating of the liner. (Page 94)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_45",
    question: "_________ are required for use on chimneys with stainless steel liners. (Page 94)",
    options: ["Rain Caps", "Washes", "Hearth Stoves", "Top Dampers"],
    answer: "Rain Caps",
  },
  {
    id: "7_46",
    question: "All flexible stainless-steel liners are supplied in 2 ft sections. (Page 94)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_47",
    question: "This liner is installed as one continuous piece. (Page 94)",
    options: ["Flexible Liners", "Rigid Liners", "Stovepipe", "Manufactured Chimneys"],
    answer: "Flexible Liners",
  },
  {
    id: "7_48",
    question: "Both Rigid and Flexible liners require Rain Caps after installation. (Page 94)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_49",
    question: "To enhance performance and reduce potential hazards, chimney liners are _________. (Page 95)",
    options: ["Wrapped in insulation", "Made of titanium", "Used only with open fireplaces", "Exposed directly to the outside"],
    answer: "Wrapped in insulation",
  },
  {
    id: "7_50",
    question: "How does an insulated liner reduce creosoted and establish draft quicker? (Page 95)",
    options: ["Keeps the liner and the inner flue gases warmer", "Does not let outside gases mix with the flue gases", "Slows the flow of gases", "Decreases the pressure difference between the outside and inside"],
    answer: "Keeps the liner and the inner flue gases warmer",
  },
  {
    id: "7_51",
    question: "Insulated pellet, oil and gas flue liners do not improve these systems. They only improve wood burning systems. (Page 95)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_52",
    question: "One common method of insulating a stainless steel liner is wrapping it with a blanket of _________. (Page 95)",
    options: ["Ceramic Wool", "Fiberglass Insulation", "Aluminum Foil", "Horse Hair Insulation"],
    answer: "Ceramic Wool",
  },
  {
    id: "7_53",
    question: "A common way of insulating a stainless steel liner is to fill the void between the liner and the chimney walls with _________. (Page 95)",
    options: ["A mixture of expanded mica, perlite, or vermiculite and cement", "Fiberglass Insulation", "Expanding Foam", "Refractory Silicone"],
    answer: "A mixture of expanded mica, perlite, or vermiculite and cement",
  },
  {
    id: "7_54",
    question: "A common way of insulating a stainless steel liner is to use pre-insulated liners that utilize a ceramic blanket and an outer layer of _________ to secure the insulation. (Page 95)",
    options: ["Aluminum or Stainless steel", "Duct Tape", "Fiberglass Insulation", "Refractory cement"],
    answer: "Aluminum or Stainless steel",
  },
  {
    id: "7_55",
    question: "In the past, stainless steel chimney liners were sometimes insulated with a loose fill of expanded mica, perlite or vermiculite without something. This could result in serious issues. For example, if the liner developed a hole, the loose fill could leak into the liner and block the thimble. What was missing from the mix? (Page 95)",
    options: ["Cement", "Silicone", "Expanding Foam", "Glue"],
    answer: "Cement",
  },
  {
    id: "7_56",
    question: "These liner systems are produced in 2 basic methods. One method uses a slurry mixture pumped into a chimney around an inflated bladder, and then after the slurry dries the bladder is deflated; the second uses a slip-form technique that packs a mixture to the chimney wall to create a continuous flue. (Page 96)",
    options: ["Flexible Liner", "Cast-In-Place Liner", "B-Vent Liner", "Rigid Liner"],
    answer: "Cast-In-Place Liner",
  },
  {
    id: "7_57",
    question: "The standard for chimney lining and re-lining systems is _________. (Page 96)",
    options: ["UL 1777", "UL 127", "UL 103", "UL 1482"],
    answer: "UL 1777",
  },
  {
    id: "7_58",
    question: "If called to sweep an unfamiliar listed liner system, you should _________. (Page 97)",
    options: ["Ask the homeowner for a copy of the installation information", "Take an educated guess based on the appliance", "Always use a Flat Wire Brush", "Immediately refuse to sweep it"],
    answer: "Ask the homeowner for a copy of the installation information",
  },
  {
    id: "7_59",
    question: "_________ are a listed venting system made as a double-walled pipe with an air space between the walls. They are used for venting listed Category 1 gas appliances, or those with draft hoods. (Page 97)",
    options: ["B-Vent", "Direct Vent", "L-Vent", "Specialty Gas Vent"],
    answer: "B-Vent",
  },
  {
    id: "7_60",
    question: "B-Vent is a single-walled pipe. (Page 97)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_61",
    question: "B-Vent vents ALL categories of gas appliances. (Page 97)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_62",
    question: "B-Vent's aluminum inner pipe is designed to withstand appliance outlet temperatures up to about _________°F. (Page 97)",
    options: ["1000", "480", "840", "500"],
    answer: "480",
  },
  {
    id: "7_63",
    question: "_________ is a vent designed to be used within a wall to vent a gas appliance that is approved for use with this vent. (Page 97)",
    options: ["B-Vent", "L-Vent", "BW Vent", "Direct Vent"],
    answer: "BW Vent",
  },
  {
    id: "7_64",
    question: "Most hearth appliances are not approved for use with BW Vent. (Page 97)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_65",
    question: "_________ units are sealed combustion systems that work by drawing outside air for combustion and expel combustion gases and by products outside the home. (Page 97)",
    options: ["B-Vent", "BW Vent", "Direct Vent", "L-Vent"],
    answer: "Direct Vent",
  },
  {
    id: "7_66",
    question: "Today approximately _________ of the new gas hearth appliances use direct vent technology. (Page 97)",
    options: ["80%", "50%", "90%", "25%"],
    answer: "80%",
  },
  {
    id: "7_67",
    question: "When using Direct Vent appliances, if the manufacturer specifies a specific brand of pipe you can use a different brand as long as they are similar. (Page 98)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_68",
    question: "Many new installations require _________ venting systems to vent direct vent appliances. These systems use a pipe inside a pipe. (Page 98)",
    options: ["Co-axial", "Co-linear", "L-Vent", "B-Vent"],
    answer: "Co-axial",
  },
  {
    id: "7_69",
    question: "Co-axial direct vents are systems where 2 pipes run side by side. (Page 98)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_70",
    question: "Direct vent fireplace inserts, most furnaces and boilers, and some factory built fireplaces may use 2 flexible aluminum liners. One is responsible to bring fresh air in, while the other exhausts the flue gases. This venting system is known as _________. (Page 98)",
    options: ["Co-linear", "Co-axial", "L-Vent", "Power Vent"],
    answer: "Co-linear",
  },
  {
    id: "7_71",
    question: "Aluminum liners are allowed to be used to vent gas fired appliances as long as they are approved for use with _________. (Page 98)",
    options: ["B-Vent", "Co-Linear Vent", "Direct Vent", "L-Vent"],
    answer: "B-Vent",
  },
  {
    id: "7_72",
    question: "In most cases, these are designed for appliances that operate under positive pressure in the venting system. They may be plastic, pvc, or metal and single or double wall. (Page 98)",
    options: ["B-Vent", "Specialty Gas Vents", "Direct Vent", "L-Vent"],
    answer: "Specialty Gas Vents",
  },
  {
    id: "7_73",
    question: "_________ are controlled devices with fans placed at the end of the vent pipe to pull the products of combustion out of the venting system (Page 99)",
    options: ["B-Vent", "Co-Linear Vent", "Co-axial Vent", "Power Vents"],
    answer: "Power Vents",
  },
  {
    id: "7_74",
    question: "Which of the following is true when it comes to differing L-Vent and B-Vent? (Page 99)",
    options: ["L-Vent uses Stainless Steel while B-Vent uses Aluminum", "L-Vent uses Aluminum while B-Vent uses Stainless Steel", "L-Vent uses Stainless Steel while B-Vent uses Titanium", "L-Vent uses Aluminum while B-Vent uses PVC"],
    answer: "L-Vent uses Stainless Steel while B-Vent uses Aluminum",
  },
  {
    id: "7_75",
    question: "Fuel oil and Pellet Appliances use this type of vent. (Page 99)",
    options: ["B-Vent", "Co-Linear Vent", "Direct Vent", "L-Vent"],
    answer: "L-Vent",
  },
  {
    id: "7_76",
    question: "L-Vent and Pellet Vent are essentially the same thing. (Page 99)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_77",
    question: "Most pellet appliances utilize _________ to pressurize the vent. (Page 99)",
    options: ["A fan", "Natural Draft", "Flow", "Top Damper"],
    answer: "A fan",
  },
  {
    id: "7_78",
    question: "Pellet Vent pipe joints must contain pressure utilizing a gasket, high-temp sealant, or special design. (Page 99)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_79",
    question: "L Vent was designed to vent oil burning appliances with flue gas temperatures of _________°F or less and flue gases high in sulfur content. (Page 99)",
    options: ["480", "570", "1000", "500"],
    answer: "570",
  },
  {
    id: "7_80",
    question: "A _________ is a plate or mechanism used to close off the venting system when not in use. (Page 99)",
    options: ["Damper", "Throat", "Baffle Plate", "Firestop"],
    answer: "Damper",
  },
  {
    id: "7_81",
    question: "You are inspecting a fireplace where the damper is located at the throat. This type of damper is called a _________. (Page 100)",
    options: ["Throat Damper", "Lintel Damper", "Top Damper", "Firebox Damper"],
    answer: "Throat Damper",
  },
  {
    id: "7_82",
    question: "Throat dampers are usually deeper than they are wide. (Page 100)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_83",
    question: "Throat Dampers consist of a pivoting _________, which opens and closes over an opening in the damper frame. (Page 100)",
    options: ["Valve Plate", "Fan", "Piston", "Gasket"],
    answer: "Valve Plate",
  },
  {
    id: "7_84",
    question: "A Damper Blade is also known as a 'Valve Plate'. (Page 100)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_85",
    question: "This type of Throat Damper contains a long rod that passes through the fireplace face. A spiral screw is mounted on the rod, and a valve plate attachment fits over this screw. As the user turns the rod from the outside, the damper opens or closes. (Page 100)",
    options: ["Rotary", "Lever", "Poker", "Twister"],
    answer: "Rotary",
  },
  {
    id: "7_86",
    question: "Removing the valve plate on a rotary type is often very easy. (Page 100)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_87",
    question: "How do you remove a Rotary type valve plate? (Page 100)",
    options: ["Usually by separating the valve plate from the rest of the damper mechanism", "You must always have to break it", "They cannot be removed", "Simply by lifting the valve plate away from the frame"],
    answer: "Usually by separating the valve plate from the rest of the damper mechanism",
  },
  {
    id: "7_88",
    question: "A lever or poker control mechanism is moved from inside the fireplace to open and shut the damper. (Page 100)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_89",
    question: "A Vestal Damper uses what mechanism? (Page 100)",
    options: ["Rotary", "Lever", "Automatic", "Twister"],
    answer: "Lever",
  },
  {
    id: "7_90",
    question: "What is the main way to remove a vestal damper? (Page 101)",
    options: ["Open the damper then remove the cotter pin to free the damper handle", "Leave it closed and lift it from the rear", "They cannot be removed", "You must cut it out"],
    answer: "Open the damper then remove the cotter pin to free the damper handle",
  },
  {
    id: "7_91",
    question: "When dealing with dampers, it is good to carry these in case they break? (Page 101)",
    options: ["Cotter Pins", "Bolts", "Levers", "Damper Frames"],
    answer: "Cotter Pins",
  },
  {
    id: "7_92",
    question: "An Allied/Donley Damper uses what mechanism? (Page 101)",
    options: ["Rotary Only", "Lever Only", "Rotary or Lever", "Automatic"],
    answer: "Rotary or Lever",
  },
  {
    id: "7_93",
    question: "Majestic dampers should be removed in the closed position. (Page 101)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_94",
    question: "What is one key differentiation about a Majestic Damper? (Page 101)",
    options: ["They have a handle with a large round hole in the center", "They are Rotary Controlled", "They are circular", "They are made of wood"],
    answer: "They have a handle with a large round hole in the center",
  },
  {
    id: "7_95",
    question: "How do you remove dampers for steel fireplace units that are manufactured as a part of the firebox? (Page 101)",
    options: ["Remove their cotter pin", "Simply lift it out", "They cannot be removed", "'Over' Open the damper to pop it out of place"],
    answer: "They cannot be removed",
  },
  {
    id: "7_96",
    question: "According to NFPA 211, what must be installed when a metal fireplace has heat exchanger tubes? (Page 102)",
    options: ["Automatic Fire Extinguisher", "Access Door that allows entry into the smoke chamber", "Top Mount Damper", "Donley Damper"],
    answer: "Access Door that allows entry into the smoke chamber",
  },
  {
    id: "7_97",
    question: "This damper is opened and closed by a cable attached to a chain and bracket located on the sidewall of the firebox. The damper itself is located on the top of the chimney? (Page 102)",
    options: ["Chimney Damper", "Top-Mounted Damper", "Flue Damper", "Damper from Above"],
    answer: "Top-Mounted Damper",
  },
  {
    id: "7_98",
    question: "Where are most dampers located for factory-built fireplaces? (Page 102)",
    options: ["Where the chimney joins the top of the firebox", "At the top of the chimney", "In the middle of the flue", "They don't have dampers that can close"],
    answer: "Where the chimney joins the top of the firebox",
  },
  {
    id: "7_99",
    question: "Connector pipe dampers should not obstruct more than _________ of the interior connector area when closed? (Page 103)",
    options: ["90%", "80%", "50%", "75%"],
    answer: "80%",
  },
  {
    id: "7_100",
    question: "This damper a valve, usually in the form of a rotating, round-plate, for controlling the flow of smoke through the connector pipe and therefore the venting system? (Page 103)",
    options: ["Chimney Damper", "Connector Damper", "Flue Damper", "Damper from Above"],
    answer: "Connector Damper",
  },
  {
    id: "7_101",
    question: "_________ Dampers are prohibited in vents for gas and oil fired appliances. (Page 103)",
    options: ["Automatic", "Manual", "Barometric", "Metal"],
    answer: "Manual",
  },
  {
    id: "7_102",
    question: "This damper fits in a t-section on the connector. It operates automatically and limits the draft that pulls air into the heating appliance. (Page 103)",
    options: ["Chimney Damper", "Barometric Damper", "Connector Damper", "Majestic Damper"],
    answer: "Barometric Damper",
  },
  {
    id: "7_103",
    question: "A barometric damper increases draft in the appliance? (Page 103)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_104",
    question: "What happens to a barometric damper when a chimney fire occurs? (Page 103)",
    options: ["Makes a loud ringing noise to alert the homeowner", "Completely closes to prevent air from fueling the chimney fire", "Completely opens resulting in air entering the flue and sustaining the fire", "Reverses Draft causing a forced downdraft"],
    answer: "Completely opens resulting in air entering the flue and sustaining the fire",
  },
  {
    id: "7_105",
    question: "Barometric dampers are highly recommended on wood burning systems. (Page 103)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_106",
    question: "A _________ fits in the connector directly behind or above the stove. This extracts heat from flue gases and pushes them to the room. (Page 103)",
    options: ["Heat Exchanger", "Heat Reclaimer", "Fan", "Barometric Damper"],
    answer: "Heat Reclaimer",
  },
  {
    id: "7_107",
    question: "Why do Heat Reclaimers increase the likelihood of excessive creosote buildup? (Page 103)",
    options: ["Cooler flue gases results in the smoke condensing in the flue", "It increases draft", "It converts Carbon Dioxide back into Carbon Monoxide", "It always generates a small fire directly in the flue"],
    answer: "Cooler flue gases results in the smoke condensing in the flue",
  },
  {
    id: "7_108",
    question: "According to the NFPA 211 and the IRC, a chimney connector must not pass through any ceiling, floor, concealed space, firewall, or fire partition while in route to the chimney. (Page 104)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_109",
    question: "IRC and NFPA 211 require that a connector to a masonry chimney must extend through the chimney wall to the _________ and be firmly cemented to the masonry. (Page 104)",
    options: ["Inner face of the flue liner, but not beyond (must be flush)", "Inner face of the flue liner, and between 1 and 3 inches beyond", "The middle of the flue to ensure gases will be contained", "Area 1 inch before the inner face of the flue liner"],
    answer: "Inner face of the flue liner, but not beyond (must be flush)",
  },
  {
    id: "7_110",
    question: "When doesn't a chimney connector not need to be cemented to the masonry? (Page 104)",
    options: ["When thimbles are used to aid in the removal of the chimney connector for cleaning", "When the diameter of the connector is 6 inches or under", "When venting a gas appliance", "When you are on the main floor of the house"],
    answer: "When thimbles are used to aid in the removal of the chimney connector for cleaning",
  },
  {
    id: "7_111",
    question: "A _________ is a fixed or removable ring, tube, or lining usually located in the hole where a chimney connector or vent connector passes through a wall or enters a chimney or vent. (Page 104)",
    options: ["Thimble", "Tee Snout", "Connector", "Flue Collar"],
    answer: "Thimble",
  },
  {
    id: "7_112",
    question: "A thimble must be permanently cemented in place with _________. (Page 104)",
    options: ["Refractory Cement", "Grout", "Refractory Silicone", "Mill-Pac"],
	answer: "Refractory Cement",
  },
  {
    id: "7_113",
    question: "Thimbles must be constructed of _________. (Page 104)",
    options: ["Fire Clay or Galvanized Steel of minimum 24-gauge thickness", "Fire Clay or Galvanized Steel of minimum 16-gauge thickness", "Galvanized Steel of minimum 22-gauge thickness", "Refractory Cement"],
	answer: "Fire Clay or Galvanized Steel of minimum 24-gauge thickness",
  },
  {
    id: "7_114",
    question: "A _________ is a type of thimble most commonly defined as a method to penetrate a combustible wall to reach a masonry chimney. (Page 104)",
    options: ["Wall Pass-Through", "24 Gauge Galvanized Steel Thimble", "Non-Combustible Thimble", "Wall Protector"],
	answer: "Wall Pass-Through",
  },
  {
    id: "7_115",
    question: "Wall Pass-Throughs are usually insulated. (Page 104)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_116",
    question: "Wood burning stoves, hearth stoves and fireplace inserts MAY NOT be connected to a masonry chimney serving a fireplace. (Page 104)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_117",
    question: "These replace a short section of the connector pipe with a specially designed heater to pre-heat the venting system so you can establish draft quicker and without a lot of smoke billowing into the room. (Page 104)",
    options: ["Heat Reclaimers", "Vent Pipe Heaters", "Heat Exchangers", "Barometric Dampers"],
	answer: "Vent Pipe Heaters",
  },
  {
    id: "7_118",
    question: "Mechanical Draft fans are able to operate without electricity. (Page 105)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_119",
    question: "_________ is designed to protect the top of a chimney and are made of masonry or metal. They help prevent rain, snow, debris, leaves, animals, and birds from entering the chimney. Screens and spark arrestors are often a part of these. (Page 105)",
    options: ["Chimney Cap", "Wash", "Crown", "Splay"],
	answer: "Chimney Cap",
  },
  {
    id: "7_120",
    question: "Premature deterioration of the firebox and liner mortar joints in a fireplace is usually a result of _________. (Page 105)",
    options: ["Water Damage", "Chimney Fires", "Bad Construction", "Creosote"],
	answer: "Water Damage",
  },
  {
    id: "7_121",
    question: "If wind-induced downdraft is caused by turbulence, a _________ may deflect the wind enough for the chimney to function normally. (Page 105)",
    options: ["Crown", "Chimney Cap", "Corbelled Chimney", "Chimney under 3 feet"],
	answer: "Chimney Cap",
  },
  {
    id: "7_122",
    question: "Most masonry fireplaces are very efficient. (Page 105)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_123",
    question: "_________ are tall and shallow to reflect more heat, and they have streamlined throats to eliminate turbulence and carry away the smoke with little loss of heated room air. (Page 106)",
    options: ["Rumford Fireplaces", "Heatilators", "Hearth Stoves", "Gas Inserts"],
	answer: "Rumford Fireplaces",
  },
  {
    id: "7_124",
    question: "Double Wall Steel Fireboxes surrounded by masonry in fireplaces was popular in this time period. (Page 106)",
    options: ["1960-1980", "1940-1950", "1990-2000", "2005-2015"],
	answer: "1960-1980",
  },
  {
    id: "7_125",
    question: "Two popular brands of Steel Fireboxes were Superior and Heatilator. (Page 106)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_126",
    question: "_________ consist of a factory-made firebox assembly and metal chimney system. They are usually enclosed within framed walls that can be covered with masonry or other materials. (Page 106)",
    options: ["Factory-Built Fireplaces", "Masonry Fireplaces", "Fireplace Insert", "Freestanding Stoves"],
	answer: "Factory-Built Fireplaces",
  },
  {
    id: "7_127",
    question: "Although most factory-built fireplaces today have some sort of minimum clearances to combustibles, they have never been able to shed the name _________. (Page 107)",
    options: ["Zero-Clearance", "Anti-combustible", "User-Friendly", "Safety-Fireplaces"],
	answer: "Zero-Clearance",
  },
  {
    id: "7_128",
    question: "Accessories can be installed on masonry and factory-built fireplaces if the accessories are listed and installed according to their listing, installed according to the manufacturer's instructions or installed by a qualified agency and are acceptable to the AHJ. (Page 107)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_129",
    question: "_________ is credited with developing the first 'mass produced' wood burning stove in this country. (Page 107)",
    options: ["Benjamin Franklin", "Elon Musk", "George Washington", "Dick Van Dyke"],
	answer: "Benjamin Franklin",
  },
  {
    id: "7_130",
    question: "New wood stove construction techniques make it possible to build stoves that are sealed much tighter, giving the control of combustion air to the operator. These quickly gained the name _________. (Page 107)",
    options: ["Zero-Clearance", "Air-Tight", "Quick Seal", "User Lenient"],
	answer: "Air-Tight",
  },
  {
    id: "7_131",
    question: "In general most stoves sold today must be EPA Approved. (Page 108)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_132",
    question: "There are _________ major types of freestanding wood stoves. (Page 108)",
    options: ["3", "4", "2", "5"],
	answer: "3",
  },
  {
    id: "7_133",
    question: "_________ are typically built from flat panels of steel 1/8 - 3/8 of an inch thick. (Page 108)",
    options: ["Steel Stoves", "Cast Iron Stoves", "Soapstone Stoves", "Titanium Stoves"],
	answer: "Steel Stoves",
  },
  {
    id: "7_134",
    question: "_________ are constructed of panels. Cast iron is poured into molds; is is not a flat piece of metal. (Page 108)",
    options: ["Steel Stoves", "Cast Iron Stoves", "Soapstone Stoves", "Titanium Stoves"],
	answer: "Cast Iron Stoves",
  },
  {
    id: "7_135",
    question: "_________ are either built with an inner firebox of steel or cast iron and stone panels, or the firebox is made from thicker soapstone panels that are exposed directly to the fire. (Page 108)",
    options: ["Steel Stoves", "Cast Iron Stoves", "Soapstone Stoves", "Titanium Stoves"],
	answer: "Soapstone Stoves",
  },
  {
    id: "7_136",
    question: "How can you tell the difference between a Steel Stove and a Cast Iron Stove? (Page 108)",
    options: ["Steel stoves have panels that are welded together, while Cast Iron Stoves have panels that are joined with tongue and groove joints, or the seams are sealed with furnace cement", "Cast Iron stoves have panels that are welded together, while Steel Stoves have panels that are joined with tongue and groove joints, or the seams are sealed with furnace cement", "Steel Stoves are usually polished and reflective, while Cast Iron Stoves are usually flat black", "Steel Stoves have soapstone panels, while Cast Iron Stoves do not"],
	answer: "Steel stoves have panels that are welded together, while Cast Iron Stoves have panels that are joined with tongue and groove joints, or the seams are sealed with furnace cement",
  },
  {
    id: "7_137",
    question: "A _________ is a device designed to increase the combustion efficiency of a wood heating system by lowering the ignition temperature of the flue gasses passing through it. (Page 108)",
    options: ["Heat Reclaimer", "Catalytic Combustor", "Heat Exchanger", "Baffle Plate"],
	answer: "Catalytic Combustor",
  },
  {
    id: "7_138",
    question: "When operating a wood stove, up to _________ of the potential energy content of the fuel is converted to a variety of gases. (Page 108)",
    options: ["20%", "40%", "50%", "10%"],
	answer: "50%",
  },
  {
    id: "7_139",
    question: "A catalytic combustor works to lower the ignition temperature of the escaping gases to approximately _________°F. (Page 109)",
    options: ["500", "900", "800", "1000"],
	answer: "500",
  },
  {
    id: "7_140",
    question: "The Catalytic Combustor's pad is coated with a combination of _________. (Page 109)",
    options: ["Noble Metal Catalysts", "Creosote Busters", "Natural Gas and LP residue", "Fuel and Oxygen"],
	answer: "Noble Metal Catalysts",
  },
  {
    id: "7_141",
    question: "If a Catalytic Combustor is glowing red, it is a VALID indication that the combustor is functioning correctly. (Page 109)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_142",
    question: "If the Catalytic Combustor is glowing red, that means it has reached _________. (Page 109)",
    options: ["500°F - 700°F", "1500°F - 1700°F", "1300°F - 1500°F", "704°F - 816°F"],
	answer: "1300°F - 1500°F",
  },
  {
    id: "7_143",
    question: "How can you verify a Catalytic Combustor is working correctly? (Page 109)",
    options: ["Insert a probe thermometer just above it; a high reading means it is working", "If it is glowing red", "Measure the temperature of the stovepipe", "If it is making a faint whistling sound"],
	answer: "Insert a probe thermometer just above it; a high reading means it is working",
  },
  {
    id: "7_144",
    question: "Catalytic Combustors never need changed. (Page 109)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_145",
    question: "What is a catalytic combustor's lifetime expressed as? (Page 109)",
    options: ["Hours of Usage", "Years", "Burning Seasons", "Months"],
	answer: "Hours of Usage",
  },
  {
    id: "7_146",
    question: "Most fireplace inserts draw air in the space between the firebox and shell so the heat from the firebox can be transferred to the room by means of _________? (Page 109)",
    options: ["Radiation", "Conduction", "Convection", "Combustion"],
	answer: "Convection",
  },
  {
    id: "7_147",
    question: "When it comes to relining a chimney for a fireplace insert, it is best to _________. (Page 109)",
    options: ["Reline all the way to the top of the chimney", "Reline to the first flue tile", "No relining is needed if the existing Terra Cotta tile is still in great shape", "Just have a small run of connector pipe into the smoke chamber"],
	answer: "Reline all the way to the top of the chimney",
  },
  {
    id: "7_148",
    question: "According to NFPA 211, all fireplace inserts require the use of a _________ chimney system. (Page 110)",
    options: ["1700°F HT", "2100°F HT", "2000°F HT", "1700°F"],
	answer: "2100°F HT",
  },
  {
    id: "7_149",
    question: "A _________ sits on the hearth and is designed with a rear flue exit that is low enough to fit under the fireplace lintel and make use of fireplace chimney. (Page 110)",
    options: ["Wood Burning Insert", "Hearth Stove", "Open Fireplace", "Freestanding Stove"],
	answer: "Hearth Stove",
  },
  {
    id: "7_150",
    question: "When it comes to Inserts and Hearth Stoves, the minimum requirement for relining the flue is _________. (Page 110)",
    options: ["You must reline all the way to the top of the chimney", "You must at least line from the appliance to the first flue tile", "You don't need a liner as long as the flue collar rests directly under the throat", "The liner must always reduce at least 2 inches in diameter between the flue collar and the stainless steel liner"],
	answer: "You must at least line from the appliance to the first flue tile",
  },
  {
    id: "7_151",
    question: "Although coal burns hotter than cordwood, all wood burning stoves are built to withstand the heat of burning coal. (Page 111)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_152",
    question: "Gas appliances now represent almost _________ of the hearth products installed today. (Page 111)",
    options: ["All", "80%", "20%", "50%"],
	answer: "80%",
  },
  {
    id: "7_153",
    question: "Chimney technicians should promote annual service for gas hearth appliances as well. (Page 111)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_154",
    question: "When it comes to gas units, if you want to convert from Natural Gas to LP, or vise versa, you can do so without the need of any modifications. (Page 111)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_155",
    question: "_________ offer the look an effect of a real wood fireplace and is the 'original' gas hearth appliance. (Page 111)",
    options: ["Gas Hearth Stove", "Gas Insert", "Gas Logs", "Wall Mounted Propane Heater"],
	answer: "Gas Logs",
  },
  {
    id: "7_156",
    question: "Gas logs can be installed in a fireplace suitable for wood burning or specifically designed for gas logs. (Page 112)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_157",
    question: "_________ are a must for LP and all vent-free logs sets. These are also required for vented natural gas sets in many jurisdictions. (Page 112)",
    options: ["Safety Pilots", "Stainless Steel Liners", "Power Vents", "Gas Leak Detectors"],
	answer: "Safety Pilots",
  },
  {
    id: "7_158",
    question: "Vented gas logs must be installed in a working fireplace with adequate draft. (Page 112)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_159",
    question: "Gas logs are a repair option for unsatisfactory chimneys or fireplaces. (Page 112)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_160",
    question: "In relations to Vented Gas Logs, the damper should be _________, as specified by the gas log manufacturer instructions. (Page 112)",
    options: ["Manually operated", "Removed or Fixed in the Open Position", "Barely cracked open", "Sealed shut"],
	answer: "Removed or Fixed in the Open Position",
  },
  {
    id: "7_161",
    question: "Factory-Built Fireplaces built before _________ were not tested for use with vent free gas appliances. (Page 112)",
    options: ["1998", "2010", "1970", "2020"],
	answer: "1998",
  },
  {
    id: "7_162",
    question: "Where must B-Vent appliances terminate? (Page 113)",
    options: ["Vertically above the roof", "Horizontally after exiting the roof", "Horizontally directly perpendicular to the appliance", "Diagonally following the pitch of the house"],
	answer: "Vertically above the roof",
  },
  {
    id: "7_163",
    question: "B-Vent appliances rely on _________ for proper venting. (Page 113)",
    options: ["Mechanical Draft", "Natural Draft", "Extremely high heat", "Hard Cordwood Species"],
	answer: "Natural Draft",
  },
  {
    id: "7_164",
    question: "Factory-built gas fireplaces using Type B venting systems normally have _________ as an integral part of the appliance. (Page 113)",
    options: ["Leak Detection", "Glass Doors", "Gas Pressure Gauge", "Ash Dump"],
	answer: "Glass Doors",
  },
  {
    id: "7_165",
    question: "Log sets are interchangeable with other log sets. (Page 113)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_166",
    question: "Direct vent gas fireplaces have operable doors. (Page 113)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_167",
    question: "Direct Vent Fireplace Inserts use a _________ venting system. (Page 114)",
    options: ["Co-Axial", "Co-Linear", "Vent-Free", "Mechanical"],
	answer: "Co-Linear",
  },
  {
    id: "7_168",
    question: "Direct Vent Gas fireplace Inserts usually have a tall venting system. With this in mind, what would happen if you don't install or adjust the appliance's restrictor plate. (Page 114)",
    options: ["Distorted 'Flame Picture'. The flames would be very short and not the relaxed flame as expected.", "The gas flames would be pulled up by the large amount of draft and cause a fire hazard.", "The draft would never allow the gas appliance to shut off.", "The Flame Picture would change to green instead of the more natural looking flame."],
	answer: "Distorted 'Flame Picture'. The flames would be very short and not the relaxed flame as expected.",
  },
  {
    id: "7_169",
    question: "Where do you find venting configurations, hearth protection requirements, and clearances to combustibles for Freestanding Direct Vent Gas Stoves. (Page 114)",
    options: ["Appliance Manufacturer", "NFPA 211", "IRC", "NFPA 54"],
	answer: "Appliance Manufacturer",
  },
  {
    id: "7_170",
    question: "The glass on a gas appliance stays cool during operation. (Page 114)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_171",
    question: "Beginning January 1, 2015 all newly manufactured glass fronted gas fireplaces, inserts and freestanding stoves were required to have an installed protective barrier if the glass exceeds _________°F during operation. (Page 115)",
    options: ["500", "172", "212", "451"],
	answer: "172",
  },
  {
    id: "7_172",
    question: "Vent-Free Gas Appliances are advertised at 99.9% efficient. (Page 115)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_173",
    question: "Vent-Free Appliances are designed to be used as a primary source of heat. (Page 115)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_174",
    question: "Vent-Free appliances are required to have a(n) _________ built into the pilot assembly. (Page 115)",
    options: ["Oxygen Depletion Sensor", "Gas Accelerator", "Leak Sensor", "Barometric Damper"],
	answer: "Oxygen Depletion Sensor",
  },
  {
    id: "7_175",
    question: "ODS shuts the appliance down if the oxygen level in the home goes below _________. (Page 115)",
    options: ["18%", "20.9%", "5%", "12%"],
	answer: "18%",
  },
  {
    id: "7_176",
    question: "Vent-Free gas appliances installed at high altitudes will experience nuisance outages and are not recommended. (Page 115)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_177",
    question: "Vent-Free appliances are limited to _________ BTUs input except in bedrooms or bathrooms. (Page 115)",
    options: ["40,000", "50,000", "8,600", "100,000"],
	answer: "40,000",
  },
  {
    id: "7_178",
    question: "Vent-Free appliances installed in bedrooms are limited to _________ BTUs. (Page 115)",
    options: ["40,000", "10,000", "6,000", "8,600"],
	answer: "10,000",
  },
  {
    id: "7_179",
    question: "Vent-Free appliances installed in bathrooms are limited to _________ BTUs. (Page 115)",
    options: ["40,000", "10,000", "6,000", "8,600"],
	answer: "6,000",
  },
  {
    id: "7_180",
    question: "Vent-Free units are not allowed in many jurisdictions to be installed in bedrooms or bathrooms. (Page 115)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_181",
    question: "The combustion of 100,000 BTUs of gas will produce approximately _________ gallon(s) of water vapor. (Page 115)",
    options: ["1", "0.5", "2", "10"],
	answer: "1",
  },
  {
    id: "7_182",
    question: "A 40,000 BTU vent-free appliance will add almost _________ gallon(s) of water into the room air every hour. (Page 115)",
    options: ["1", "0.5", "2", "10"],
	answer: "0.5",
  },
  {
    id: "7_183",
    question: "You can smell carbon monoxide. (Page 116)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_184",
    question: "This category of gas appliance has flue gas temperatures hot enough to prevent condensation and vent by natural draft. (Page 116)",
    options: ["Category I", "Category II", "Category III", "Category IV"],
	answer: "Category I",
  },
  {
    id: "7_185",
    question: "This category of gas appliance is a negative pressure condensing unit whose category is not currently being used. (Page 116)",
    options: ["Category I", "Category II", "Category III", "Category IV"],
	answer: "Category II",
  },
  {
    id: "7_186",
    question: "This category of gas appliance is a positive pressure non-condensing unit. These are in use, but not that common. (Page 116)",
    options: ["Category I", "Category II", "Category III", "Category IV"],
	answer: "Category III",
  },
  {
    id: "7_187",
    question: "This category of gas appliance has a mechanical draft system that provides positive vent pressure and functions with temperatures low enough to allow condensation, which is a result of extremely high efficiencies. (Page 116)",
    options: ["Category I", "Category II", "Category III", "Category IV"],
	answer: "Category IV",
  },
  {
    id: "7_188",
    question: "Most Pellet stoves are electrically driven. (Page 116)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_189",
    question: "For the most part, pellet stoves produce heat by _________. (Page 116)",
    options: ["Convection", "Radiation", "Conduction", "Electricity"],
	answer: "Convection",
  },
  {
    id: "7_190",
    question: "Pellet stoves blow room air across a(n) _________. (Page 117)",
    options: ["Internal Heat Exchanger", "Auger", "Firepot", "Condensing Unit"],
	answer: "Internal Heat Exchanger",
  },
  {
    id: "7_191",
    question: "At this time there are loads of pellet fireplaces on the market. (Page 117)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: "7_192",
    question: "When it comes to Freestanding Pellet Appliances, the mechanical draft system allows venting straight through the wall. (Page 117)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: "7_193",
    question: "Why do some manufacturers recommend, while others require, enough vertical rise in a Pellet Appliance's venting system to create enough natural draft. (Page 116)",
    options: ["The pellets burning at the time of a power outage can push smoke into the home", "Pellets don't burn hot", "Because the mechanical draft system of a pellet appliance does not allow venting straight through a wall", "It is required in the IRC"],
	answer: "The pellets burning at the time of a power outage can push smoke into the home",
  },
  {
    id: "7_194",
    question: "In the Northeast fuel oil remains a major fuel for home heating. (Page 117)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
	answer: "True",
  },
];

if (!window.quizRegistry) window.quizRegistry = {};
window.quizRegistry['Chapter 7: Identifying Appliance and Venting System Types'] = essentialsChapter7QuizData;
